intently.co 2019-12-16

# Intently.co - Privacy

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use our services.

### In general

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We will never sell your personal data and promise to keep your details safe and secure.

When you use the service, regardless of whether you have signed up, we store information about how you use the service to help us to improve it. We use the information you provide us for the following purposes:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * Publication of requests on this site, and syndication to other websites (including via our API)
  * Sharing of requests and services with other Intently users and/or external service providers (via our API).
  * Sharing of information you have provided about you or your company with buyers (or potential buyers) when you act as a supplier (we will show the buyer your visible name, email address, website, phone number, and other information about you or your company).
  * Publication of any testimonials or quotes you may have provided regarding Intently.
  * To improve our service.
  * We may periodically send emails to you (using the email address you provided) regarding changes and improvements to our service, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting. We will always give you the option to unsubscribe from such emails, and you can change your email preferences by editing your profile. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or phone, and again you may request that we do not do this in future.

### As a buyer

It is very important for you to understand that our service is designed to make your requests visible to others, while we keep your identity anonymous. Therefore, when you create a request, the text you enter in the "what", "where", "when" and "other information" fields will be visible on the Internet. We will not publish your personal details intentionally, but if you enter your personal details into any of the aforementioned fields, then that will be made visible to others on the Internet by design.

When you sign up to use our service as a buyer, we request the following information from you:

  * Your username
  * Your email address

### As a seller

When you sign up as a seller, we ask you to provide a variety of information about your business and services including:

  * Your username
  * Your company name
  * Your website url
  * Various other information and services

We publish this information in a number of places on our website, always with the intention of promoting your business. 

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we hold about you. 

### Account administration

From time to time, one of our administrators may edit your list of services to ensure that you are getting the best possible supplier alerts based on requests being raised by users. In addition, if you are signed up and raise a request, we may occasionally raise a further request on your behalf if we feel that we can better target potential suppliers for your needs. 

If we detect that your account's email address has become invalid, then we may research and assign an alternative valid email address for your account. If we are unable to do this, then we may delete your account. Further to this, if we determine that the website assigned to your account is no longer in service, then we may delete your account. This helps to ensure that we maintain a system of valid email addresses and websites displayed on Intently. 

### Cookies

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the Internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, computer or mobile phone. These include small files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally. These pieces of information are used to improve services for you through, for example: 

  * Enabling our service to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information several times during one task.
  * Recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don't need to do it for every web page requested.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Declining cookies will prevent you from taking full advantage of our service. 

Note that we also use a few third party tools to monitor the use of our system. These tools are Google Analytics, HEAP Analytics, Trustpilot and Mouseflow, and they use cookies in order to work correctly. Our only purpose behind using these tools is to learn more about how our system is used. Please read their privay policies to understand what they do with your personal data and how you can opt out if necessary. 

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

### Freedom of information

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us at support@intently.co. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at support@intently.co. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect, or we will delete the information at your request. 

### Withdrawing consent

If you no longer consent to us storing and using your personal information in the ways described above, then please cancel your account by visiting your profile page and clikcing "Cancel account". When you cancel your account, we will delete all of the information you have provided to us about you and your company. We will also delete all of the data you have created through using our service (e.g. requests, services, business profile information, and conversations with other people on the system).
